Inventory of the Ultimate weapon: the H-bomb dilemma video tape
Hoover Institution Archives
Ultimate weapon: the H-bomb dilemma video tape
1987-2000
2003C42
1 item (18 tape boxes and 14 oversize boxes containing 172 U-Matic tapes and 208 Betacam tapes) (15 linear feet)
Hoover Institution Archives Stanford, California 94305-6010
Videotape raw footage, relating to the American decision to develop the hydrogen bomb. Used in preparation of the television program produced by the History Channel. Includes interviews with scientists and government officials involved in the decision.
Administrative Information
Access
Collection is open for research.
The Hoover Institution Archives only allows access to copies of audiovisual items. To listen to sound recordings or to view videos or films during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all audiovisual material is immediately accessible.
Acquisition Information
Acquired by the Hoover Institution Archives in 2003.
Accruals
Materials may have been added to the collection since this finding aid was prepared. To determine if this has occurred, find the collection in Stanford University's online catalog at http://searchworks.stanford.edu/. Materials have been added to the collection if the number of boxes listed in the online catalog is larger than the number of boxes listed in this finding aid.
Scope and Content of Collection
Videotape raw footage, relating to the American decision to develop the hydrogen bomb. Used in preparation of the television program produced by the History Channel. Includes interviews with scientists and government officials involved in the decision.
Videotapes include a variety of interviews with those involved in the Manhattan Project, or with knowledge regarding the "Superbomb" and its subsequent use and purpose. Contributors include Edward Teller, Robert Krohn, George Cowan, Robert Johnson, Vasily Ginzberg, Kenneth Pitzer, Emil Konopinski, Barton Bernstein, John Manely, Hans Bethe, Ted and Caro Taylor, Kenneth Ford, Françoise Ulam, Paul Nitze, Gordon Arnison, Foster Evans, Carson Marks, Louis Rosen, Norris Bradbury, Professor John Wheeler, Nicholas Metropolis, Robert Serber, Professor Rabbi, Richard Garwin, Herbet York, Frederick Reines, Victor Weisskopf, Peter Hoving, Greg McCleary. Videotapes also include historic footage and versions of the television program produced.
Arrangement
Arranged chronologically. Dates, titles and notes were taken directly from the tape label; the content of the recording may not exactly match the label.
Indexing Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the library's online public access catalog.
Hydrogen bomb.; Nuclear weapons.; United States--Armed Forces.; Videotapes.; History Channel (Television network)
Collection Contents
- 1987
  - #1 "Superbomb" Hans Bethe, Ithaca, 11 Dec 1987; Betacam, Pam Hogan Producer, TC=0=21 (Box 21)
  - #3 Hans Bethe "Superbomb", 11 Dec 1987; Betacam (Box 26)
  - #4 "Superbomb", 11 Dec 1987; Betacam (Box 30)
  - #5 Hans Bethe, "Superbomb", 11 Dec 1987; Betacam (Box 30)
  - #6 "Superbomb" Be the-end and Cornell Exteriors, 11 Dec 1987; Betacam (for the Hans Bethe Interview) (Box 21)
  - #10 "Superbomb" Robert Serber Interview, 14 Dec 1987; Betacam, Dolby on/ Dropframe (Box 32)
  - #11 "Superbomb" Robert Serber Interview, 14 Dec 1987; Betacam (Box 29)
  - #7 RABI Interview "Superbomb", 14 Dec 1987; Betacam, Note: Channel 1 and 2 are same (1 Mic Used), Dolby on dropframe (Box 29)
  - #8 "Superbomb" Robert Serber Interview, 14 Dec 1987; Betacam, Dolby on/dropframe, Channel 2= Questions, Channel 1= Answers (Box 29)
  - #9 "Superbomb" Robert Serber Interview, 14 Dec 1987; Betacam, Dolby on/dropframe, Channel 2= Questions, Channel 1= Subject (Box 25)
  - Phil Burton Productions "Superbomb" Reel #11 Robert Serber, 15 Dec 1987; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code (Box 30)
  - Phil Burton Productions "Superbomb" Hans Bethe Reel #1, 15 Dec 1987; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code (Box 30)
  - Phil Burton Productions "Superbomb" Hans Bethe Reel #2, 15 Dec 1987; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code (Box 30)
  - Phil Burton Productions "Superbomb" Hans Bethe Reel #3, 15 Dec 1987; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code (Box 31)
  - Phil Burton Productions "Superbomb" Hans Bethe Reel #4, 15 Dec 1987; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code (Box 31)
  - Phil Burton Productions "Superbomb" Hans Bethe Reel #5, 15 Dec 1987; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code (Box 31)
  - Phil Burton Productions "Superbomb" Hans Bethe Reel #6, 15 Dec 1987; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code (Box 31)
  - Phil Burton Productions "Superbomb" Professor Isidor Rabi Reel #7, 15 Dec 1987; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code (Box 32)
  - Phil Burton Productions "Superbomb" Robert Serber Reel #10, 15 Dec 1987; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code (Box 32)
  - Phil Burton Productions "Superbomb" Robert Serber Reel #8, 15 Dec 1987; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code (Box 32)
  - Phil Burton Productions "Superbomb" Robert Serber Reel #9, 15 Dec 1987; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code (Box 32)
  - "Superbomb" Kenneth Ford #20, 17 Dec 1987; Betacam (Box 26)
  - # 13 "Superbomb" John Wheeler, 17 Dec 1987; Betacam, At Princeton (Box 31)
  - # 14 "Superbomb" John Wheeler, 17 Dec 1987; Betacam, At Princeton (Box 31)
  - #12 John Wheeler, Princeton, 17 Dec 1987; Betacam (Box 29)
  - #16 John Wheeler "Superbomb", 17 Dec 1987; Betacam (Box 28)
  - #17 "Superbomb" Kenneth Ford, 17 Dec 1987; Betacam (Box 25)
  - #18 "Superbomb" (End John Wheeler, Begin Kenneth Ford), 17 Dec 1987; Betacam (Box 29)
  - #19 "Superbomb" Kenneth Ford, 17 Dec 1987; Betacam (Box 32)
  - #21 Kenneth Ford, "Superbomb", 17 Dec 1987; Betacam (Box 25)
  - #22 Kenneth Ford, "Superbomb", 17 Dec 1987; Betacam, TC 7:02 (Box 25)
  - "Superbomb" Kenneth Ford #20, 17 Dec 1987; Betacam (Box 25)
  - # 15 "Superbomb" John Wheeler, 17 Dec 1987; Betacam, At Princeton (Box 14)
  - Phil Burton Productions H-Bomb John Wheeler Reel #12, 19 Dec 1987; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code (Box 20)
  - Phil Burton Productions H-Bomb John Wheeler Reel #13, 19 Dec 1987; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code (Box 20)
  - Phil Burton Productions H-Bomb John Wheeler Reel #14, 19 Dec 1987; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code (Box 20)
  - Phil Burton Productions H-Bomb John Wheeler Reel #15, 19 Dec 1987; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code (Box 20)
  - Phil Burton Productions H-Bomb John Wheeler End, Kenneth Ford Begin Reel #18, 20 Dec 1987; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code (Box 21)
  - Phil Burton Productions H-Bomb John Wheeler Reel #16, 20 Dec 1987; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code (Box 20)
  - Phil Burton Productions H-Bomb John Wheeler Reel #17, 20 Dec 1987; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code (Box 21)
  - Phil Burton Productions H-Bomb Kenneth Ford Reel #19, 20 Dec 1987; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code (Box 20)
  - Phil Burton Productions H-Bomb Kenneth Ford Reel #20, 20 Dec 1987; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code (Box 24)
  - Phil Burton Productions H-Bomb Kenneth Ford Reel #21, 20 Dec 1987; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code (Box 24)
  - Phil Burton Productions H-Bomb Kenneth Ford Reel #22, 20 Dec 1987; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code (Box 21)
- 1988
  - "Superbomb" Eduward Teller Interview #27, 12 Jun 1988; Betacam, Ch1. Primary (Box 27)
  - "Superbomb" Edward Teller Interview #24, 12 Jun 1988; Betacam, Camera=Robin Hirsch Sound=Charles Dixon (Box 29)
  - #23 Edward Teller, "Superbomb", 12 Jun 1988; Betacam, Interview with Edward Teller, Dropframe, Dolby on TC 1:20 (Box 19)
  - #25 Edward Teller, "Superbomb", 12 Jun 1988; Betacam, Teller Interview (cont.) (Box 19)
  - #26 Edward Teller, "Superbomb", 12 Jun 1988; Betacam, Teller Interview (cont.) (Box 19)
  - #28 Edward Teller, "Superbomb", 12 Jun 1988; Betacam, Interview with Edward Teller (Box 19)
  - Edward Teller Interview "Superbomb", 12 Jun 1988; Betacam (Box 24)
  - Edward Teller "Superbomb", 12 Jun 1988; Betacam (Box 21)
  - Pam Hogan Productions "Superbomb" Edward Teller Interview Reel #23, 13 Jul 1988; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code (Box 23)
  - Pam Hogan Productions "Superbomb" Edward Teller Interview Reel #24, 13 Jul 1988; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code (Box 23)
  - Pam Hogan Productions "Superbomb" Edward Teller Interview Reel #25, 13 Jul 1988; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code (Box 23)
  - Pam Hogan Productions "Superbomb" Edward Teller Interview Reel #26, 13 Jul 1988; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code (Box 23)
  - Pam Hogan Productions "Superbomb" Edward Teller Interview Reel #27, 13 Jul 1988; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code (Box 23)
  - Pam Hogan Productions "Superbomb" Edward Teller Interview Reel #28, 13 Jul 1988; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code (Box 23)
  - #31 "Superbomb" Françoise Ulum, Sante Fe, New Mexico, 27 Jul 1988; Betacam, Interview with Françoise Ulum, Cam= de Segonzac, Sound=Karp (Box 21)
  - #32 "Superbomb" Louis Rosen Los Alamos National Lab, NM, 27 Jul 1988; Betacam, Interview with Louis Rosen, Camera= de Segonzac, Sound= Karp, Drop Frame (Box 21)
  - #33 "Superbomb" Louis Rosen Los Alamos National Lab, 27 Jul 1988; Betacam, Interview with Louis Rosen, Camera= de Segonzac, Sound= Karp, Drop Frame (Box 23)
  - #34 "Superbomb" Louis Rosen Los Alamos National Lab, 27 Jul 1988; Betacam, Interview with Louis Rosen, Camera= de Segonzac, Sound= Karp, Drop Frame (Box 23)
  - #35 "Superbomb" Louis Rosen Los Alamos National Lab, 27 Jul 1988; Betacam, Interview with Louis Rosen, Camera= de Segonzac, Sound= Karp, Drop Frame (Box 22)
  - #36 "Superbomb" Louis Rosen Los Alamos National Lab, 27 Jul 1988; Betacam, End Interview with Louis Rosen, and Mountains 7/28/88 (Box 22)
  - "Superbomb" Int. with Françoise Ulum Santa Fe, NM, 27 Jul 1988; Betacam (Box 22)
  - "Superbomb" Int. with Françoise Ulum Santa Fe, NM, 27 Jul 1988; Betacam (Box 22)
  - "Superbomb" Int. with Françoise Ulam Santa Fe, NM #30, 27 Jul 1988; Betacam, Cam= de Segonzac, Sound=Karp (Box 23)
  - "Superbomb" Int. with Françoise Ulam Santa Fe, NM #29, 27 Jul 1988; Betacam, Cam= de Segonzac, Sound=Karp (Box 22)
  - "Superbomb" Carson Marks Los Alamos, NM #43, 28 Jul 1988; Betacam (Box 23)
  - #37 Foster Evans, "Superbomb" Los Alamos, NM, 28 Jul 1988; Betacam, Cam= de Segonzac, Sound=Karp (Box 20)
  - #38 Foster Evans "Superbomb" Los Alamos, NM, 28 Jul 1988; Betacam (Box 21)
  - #39 Foster Evans, "Superbomb" Los Alamos, NM, 28 Jul 1988; Betacam, Interview (cont.) (Box 22)
  - #40 Foster Evans "Superbomb" Los Alamos, NM, 28 Jul 1988; Betacam (Box 23)
  - #41 Carson Marks "Superbomb" Los Alamos, NM, 28 Jul 1988; Betacam (Box 22)
  - #42 Carson Marks "Superbomb" Los Alamos, NM, 28 Jul 1988; Betacam (Box 21)
  - #44 Carson Marks "Superbomb" Los Alamos, NM, 28 Jul 1988; Betacam, #44/(7/28) Camera= de Segonzde, Sound=Karp (Box 21)
  - #45 Carson Marks "Superbomb" Los Alamos, NM, 28 Jul 1988; Betacam (Box 21)
  - Carson Marks #43, 28 Jul 1988; Betacam (Box 21)
  - "Superbomb" Interview With John Manely #56 Los Alamos, NM, 29 Jul 1988; Betacam, Begin Interview (Box 20)
  - "Superbomb" Jay Wechsler #65, 29 Jul 1988; Betacam, Begin. (Box 20)
  - "Superbomb" Jay Wechsler #66, 29 Jul 1988; Betacam, End. (Box 20)
  - "Superbomb" Los Alamos, NM George Cowan #63, 29 Jul 1988; Betacam (cont.) (Box 20)
  - "Superbomb" Los Alamos, NM George Cowan #64, 29 Jul 1988; Betacam, End. (Box 19)
  - #46 Norris Bradbury "Superbomb" Los Alamos, NM, 29 Jul 1988; Betacam, Begin Interview, cam=de Segonzac, Sound= Karp (Box 19)
  - #47 Norris Bradbury "Superbomb" Los Alamos, NM, 29 Jul 1988; Betacam (Box 19)
  - #48 Norris Bradbury "Superbomb" Los Alamos, NM, 29 Jul 1988; Betacam (Box 19)
  - #49 Norris Bradbury "Superbomb" Los Alamos, NM, 29 Jul 1988; Betacam, Interview with Norris Bradbury (Box 19)
  - #50 Norris Bradbury "Superbomb" Los Alamos, NM, 29 Jul 1988; Betacam, Interview with Norris Bradbury (Box 19)
  - #51 Norris Bradbury "Superbomb" Los Alamos, NM, 29 Jul 1988; Betacam, End (Box 19)
  - #52 Nicholas Metropolis "Superbomb" Los Alamos, NM, 29 Jul 1988; Betacam, Interview, Begin (Box 19)
  - #53 "Superbomb" Los Alamos, NM Nicholas Metropolis (cont.), 29 Jul 1988; Betacam, Interview with Nicholas Metropolis (Box 20)
  - #54 "Superbomb" Los Alamos, NM Nicholas Metropolis, 29 Jul 1988; Betacam (Box 19)
  - #55 "Superbomb" Nicholas Metropolis, 29 Jul 1988; Betacam (Box 19)
  - #57 John Manley "Superbomb" Los Alamos, NM, 29 Jul 1988; Betacam (Cont.) (Box 19)
  - #58 John Manely "Superbomb" Los Alamos, NM, 29 Jul 1988; Betacam (Cont.) (Box 20)
  - #59 John Manely "Superbomb" Los Alamos, NM, 29 Jul 1988; Betacam (Cont.) (Box 20)
  - #60 John Manely "Superbomb" Los Alamos, NM, 29 Jul 1988; Betacam, End (Box 20)
  - #61 George Cowan "Superbomb" Los Alamos, NM, 29 Jul 1988; Betacam, Begin (Box 27)
  - #62 Geroge Cowan "Superbomb" Los Alamos, NM, 29 Jul 1988; Betacam (Cont.) (Box 25)
  - John Manley "Superbomb" #56, 29 Jul 1988; Betacam (Box 26)
  - "Superbomb" Robert Krohn Las Lunas, NM #68, 31 Jul 1988; Betacam (Box 5)
  - "Superbomb" Robert Krohn Las Lunas, NM #69, 31 Jul 1988; Betacam, End. (Box 4)
  - Robert Krohn "Superbomb" Las Lunas, NM #67, 31 Jul 1988; Betacam, Begin Interview (Box 4)
  - Robert Krohn "Superbomb" #67, 31 Jul 1988; Betacam (Box 4)
  - Robert Krohn "Superbomb" #68, 31 Jul 1988; Betacam (Box 4)
  - Superbomb Documentary Film, Inc. "Superbomb" Reel #29 Françoise Ulam, 2 Aug 1988; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code (Box 5)
  - Superbomb Documentary Film, Inc. "Superbomb" Reel #30 Françoise Ulam, 2 Aug 1988; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code (Box 4)
  - Superbomb Documentary Film, Inc. "Superbomb" Reel #31 Françoise Ulam, 2 Aug 1988; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code (Box 12)
  - Superbomb Documentary Film, Inc. "Superbomb" Reel #32 Louis Rosen, 2 Aug 1988; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code (Box 12)
  - Superbomb Documentary Film, Inc. "Superbomb" Reel #33 Louis Rosen, 2 Aug 1988; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code (Box 26)
  - Superbomb Documentary Film, Inc. "Superbomb" Reel #34 Louis Rosen, 2 Aug 1988; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code (Box 31)
  - Superbomb Documentary Film, Inc. "Superbomb" Reel #35 Louis Rosen, 2 Aug 1988; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code (Box 30)
  - Superbomb Documentary Film, Inc. "Superbomb" Reel #36 Louis Rosen, 3 Aug 1988; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code (Box 30)
  - Superbomb Documentary Film, Inc. "Superbomb" Reel #37 Foster Evans, 3 Aug 1988; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code (Box 12)
  - Superbomb Documentary Film, Inc. "Superbomb" Reel #38 Foster Evans, 3 Aug 1988; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code (Box 7)
  - Superbomb Documentary Film, Inc. "Superbomb" Reel #39 Foster Evans, 3 Aug 1988; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code (Box 26)
  - Superbomb Documentary Film, Inc. "Superbomb" Reel #40 Foster Evans, 3 Aug 1988; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code (Box 26)
  - Superbomb Documentary Film, Inc. "Superbomb" Reel #41 Carson Mark, 3 Aug 1988; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code (Box 27)
  - Superbomb Documentary Film, Inc. "Superbomb" Reel #42 Carson Mark, 3 Aug 1988; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code (Box 25)
  - Superbomb Documentary Film, Inc. "Superbomb" Reel #43 Carson Mark, 3 Aug 1988; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code (Box 27)
  - Superbomb Documentary Film, Inc. "Superbomb" Reel #44 Carson Mark, 3 Aug 1988; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code (Box 29)
  - Superbomb Documentary Film, Inc. "Superbomb" Reel #45 Carson Mark, 3 Aug 1988; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code (Box 31)
  - Superbomb Documentary Film, Inc. "Superbomb" Reel #46 Carson Mark, 3 Aug 1988; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code (Box 31)
  - Superbomb Documentary Film, Inc. "Superbomb" Reel #47 Norris Bradbury, 3 Aug 1988; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code (Box 30)
  - Superbomb Documentary Film, Inc. "Superbomb" Reel #48 Norris Bradbury, 3 Aug 1988; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code (Box 30)
  - Superbomb Documentary Film, Inc. "Superbomb" Reel #49 Norris Bradbury, 3 Aug 1988; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code (Box 30)
  - Superbomb Documentary Film, Inc. "Superbomb" Reel #50 Norris Bradbury, 3 Aug 1988; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code (Box 31)
  - Superbomb Documentary Film, Inc. "Superbomb" Reel #51 Norris Bradbury, 3 Aug 1988; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code (Box 24)
  - Superbomb Documentary Film, Inc. "Superbomb" Reel #52 Nicholas Metropolis, 3 Aug 1988; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code (Box 28)
  - Superbomb Documentary Film, Inc. "Superbomb" Reel #53 Nicholas Metropolis, 3 Aug 1988; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code (Box 25)
  - Superbomb Documentary Film, Inc. "Superbomb" Reel #54 Nicholas Metropolis, 3 Aug 1988; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code (Box 28)
  - Superbomb Documentary Film, Inc. "Superbomb" Reel #55 Nicholas Metropolis, 3 Aug 1988; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code (Box 30)
  - Superbomb Documentary Film, Inc. "Superbomb" Reel #56 John Manely, 3 Aug 1988; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code (Box 30)
  - Superbomb Documentary Film, Inc. "Superbomb" Reel #57 John Manely, 3 Aug 1988; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code (Box 31)
  - Superbomb Documentary Film, Inc. "Superbomb" Reel #58 John Manely, 3 Aug 1988; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code (Box 25)
  - Superbomb Documentary Film, Inc. "Superbomb" Reel #59 John Manely, 3 Aug 1988; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code (Box 1)
  - Superbomb Documentary Film, Inc. "Superbomb" Reel #60 John Manely, 3 Aug 1988; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code (Box 27)
  - Superbomb Documentary Film, Inc. "Superbomb" Reel #61, George Cowan, 3 Aug 1988; U-Matic, Dub With Visual TC (Box 6)
  - Superbomb Documentary Film, Inc. "Superbomb" Reel #62 George Cowan, 3 Aug 1988; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code (Box 2)
  - Superbomb Documentary Film, Inc. "Superbomb" Reel #63, George Cowan, 3 Aug 1988; U-Matic, Dub with Visual Time Code (Box 2)
  - Superbomb Documentary Film, Inc. "Superbomb" Reel #64, George Cowan, 3 Aug 1988; U-Matic, Dub with Visual Time Code (Box 5)
  - Superbomb Documentary Film, Inc. "Superbomb" Reel #65, Jay Wechsler, 3 Aug 1988; U-Matic, Dub with Visual Time Code (Box 1)
  - Superbomb Documentary Film, Inc. "Superbomb" Reel #66, Jay Wechsler, 3 Aug 1988; U-Matic, Dub with Visual Time Code (Box 6)
  - Superbomb Documentary Film, Inc. "Superbomb" Reel #67, Robert Krohn, Los Alamos Views, 3 Aug 1988; U-Matic, Dub with Visual Time Code (Box 32)
  - Superbomb Documentary Film, Inc. "Superbomb" Reel #68, Robert Krohn, 3 Aug 1988; U-Matic, Dub with Visual Time Code (Box 6)
  - Superbomb Documentary Film, Inc. "Superbomb" Reel #69, 3 Aug 1988; U-Matic, Dub with Visual Time Code (Box 32)
  - Tea with Ms. Roosevelt, 27 Sep 1988; U-Matic (Box 7)
  - "Superbomb" Interview With Reines Production: Pam Hogan #76, 17 Oct 1988; Betacam, Irvine, CA (Box 32)
  - "Superbomb" Interview With Reines Production: Pam Hogan #78, 17 Oct 1988; Betacam, Irvine, CA (Box 6)
  - "Superbomb" Production. Pam Hogan Interview: Reines #76, 17 Oct 1988; Betacam (Box 31)
  - "Superbomb" Reines Interview Reel #75, 17 Oct 1988; U-Matic, Dub with Visual Time Code 10/25/88 (Box 1)
  - "Superbomb" Reines Interview Reel #76, 17 Oct 1988; U-Matic, Dub with Visual Time Code 10/25/88 (Box 25)
  - "Superbomb" Reines Interview Reel #77, 17 Oct 1988; U-Matic, Dub with Visual Time Code 10/25/88 (Box 29)
  - "Superbomb" Reines Interview Reel #78, 17 Oct 1988; U-Matic, Dub With Visual TC 10/25/88 (Box 1)
  - "Superbomb" Reines Production: Pam Hogan #75, 17 Oct 1988; Betacam (Box 24)
  - "Superbomb" Reines Production: Pam Hogan #77, 17 Oct 1988; Betacam, Interview in Irivine, CA (Box 27)
  - "Superbomb" Roll 70 York Inc. Production. Pam Hogan, 17 Oct 1988; Betacam (Box 2)
  - "Superbomb" Roll 71 York Inc. Production. Pam Hogan, 17 Oct 1988; Betacam, La Jolla, CA (Box 28)
  - "Superbomb" York Inc. Production: Pam Hogan #71, 17 Oct 1988; Betacam (Box 27)
  - "Superbomb" York Inc. Production: Pam Hogan #72, 17 Oct 1988; Betacam (Box 7)
  - "Superbomb" York Inc. Production: Pam Hogan #73, 17 Oct 1988; Betacam (Box 27)
  - "Superbomb" York Inc. Production: Pam Hogan #74, 17 Oct 1988; Betacam (Box 28)
  - "Superbomb" York Inc. Production: Pam Hogan Roll 70, 17 Oct 1988; Betacam (Box 1)
  - "Superbomb" Herbet York Interview, 17 Oct 1988; U-Matic, Reel #70, Dub with Visual Time Code (Box 31)
  - "Superbomb" Herbet York Interview, 17 Oct 1988; U-Matic, Reel #71, Dub with Visual Time Code (Box 1)
  - "Superbomb" Herbet York Interview, 17 Oct 1988; U-Matic, Reel #72, Dub with Visual Time Code (Box 32)
  - "Superbomb" Herbet York Interview, 17 Oct 1988; U-Matic, Reel #73, Dub with Visual Time Code (Box 1)
  - "Superbomb" Herbet York Interview, 17 Oct 1988; U-Matic, Reel #74, Dub with Visual Time Code (Box 25)
  - "Superbomb" Interview With Kenneth Pitzer #80, 19 Oct 1988; Betacam, Ch1/3 = Kenneth Pitzer, Ch2/4 = Pam and Peter, At UC Berkeley (Box 27)
  - "Superbomb" Interview With Kenneth Pitzer #81, 19 Oct 1988; Betacam, Ch1/3 = Kenneth Pitzer, Ch2/4 = Pam and Peter, At UC Berkeley (Box 16)
  - "Superbomb" Interview With Kenneth Pitzer #82, 19 Oct 1988; Betacam, Ch1/3 = Kenneth Pitzer, Ch2/4 = Pam and Peter, At UC Berkeley (Box 10)
  - "Superbomb" Interview With Kenneth Pitzer #82, 19 Oct 1988; Betacam, Ch1/3 = Kenneth Pitzer, Ch2/4 = Pam and Peter, At UC Berkeley (Box 11)
  - "Superbomb" Kenneth Pitzer Interview Reel #79, 19 Oct 1988; U-Matic, Dub With Visual TC 10/25/88 (Box 11)
  - "Superbomb" Kenneth Pitzer Interview Reel #80, 19 Oct 1988; U-Matic, Dub With Visual TC 10/25/88 (Box 11)
  - "Superbomb" Kenneth Pitzer Interview Reel #81, 19 Oct 1988; U-Matic, Dub With Visual TC 10/25/88 (Box 11)
  - "Superbomb" Kenneth Pitzer Interview Reel #82, 19 Oct 1988; U-Matic, Dub With Visual TC 10/25/88 (Box 2)
  - "Superbomb" Seismograph B-Roll Reel #83, 19 Oct 1988; Betacam (Box 1)
  - "Superbomb" Seismograph-UC Berkeley Reel #83, 19 Oct 1988; U-Matic, Dub With Visual TC 10/25/88 (Box 2)
  - Indiana University Interview With Emil Konopinski #84 H Bomb, 29 Oct 1988; Betacam, Audio 1- Konop, Audio 2-Hogan-Galinos (Box 27)
  - Indiana University Interview With Emil Konopinski #85 H Bomb, 29 Oct 1988; Betacam, Audio 1- Konop, Audio 2-Hogan-Galinos (Box 11)
  - Indiana University Interview With Emil Konopinski #86 H Bomb, 29 Oct 1988; Betacam, Audio 1- Konop, Audio 2-Hogan-Galinos (Box 16)
  - Indiana University Interview With Emil Konopinski #87 H Bomb, 29 Oct 1988; Betacam, Audio 1- Konop, Audio 2-Hogan-Galinos (Box 18)
  - Indiana University Interview With Emil Konopinski #88 H Bomb, 29 Oct 1988; Betacam, Audio 1- Konop, Audio 2-Hogan-Galinos (Box 16)
  - Indiana University Interview With Emil Konopinski #89 H Bomb, 29 Oct 1988; Betacam, Audio 1- Konop, Audio 2-Hogan-Galinos (Box 16)
  - Indiana University Interview With Emil Konopinski #90 H Bomb, 29 Oct 1988; Betacam (Box 16)
  - Indiana University Interview With Emil Konopinski #84, 29 Oct 1988; Betacam (Box 17)
  - Indiana University Interview With Emil Konopinski #88, 29 Oct 1988; Betacam (Box 17)
  - "Superbomb" H-Bomb Emil Konopinski Tape #84, 29 Oct 1988; U-Matic, Dub With Visual TC 11/7/88 (Box 17)
  - "Superbomb" H-Bomb Emil Konopinski Tape #85, 29 Oct 1988; U-Matic, Dub With Visual TC 11/7/88 (Box 16)
  - "Superbomb" H-Bomb Emil Konopinski Tape #86, 29 Oct 1988; U-Matic, Dub With Visual TC 11/7/88 (Box 16)
  - "Superbomb" H-Bomb Emil Konopinski Tape #87, 29 Oct 1988; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code 11/7/88 (Box 16)
  - "Superbomb" H-Bomb Emil Konopinski Tape #88, 29 Oct 1988; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code 11/7/88 (Box 17)
  - "Superbomb" H-Bomb Emil Konopinski Tape #89, 29 Oct 1988; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code 11/7/88 (Box 16)
  - "Superbomb" H-Bomb Emil Konopinski Tape #90, 29 Oct 1988; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code 11/7/88 (Box 17)